https://demolitionparts.com/info/privacy/

PRIVACY
Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information
Thank you for visiting DEMOLITION PARTS and all of it’s affiliates; volumebikes.com. This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. OUR ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES MAY DIFFER FROM OUR PRACTICES REGARDING INFORMATION OBTAINED OFFLINE.
REMEMBER IF YOU REGISTER WITH DEMOLITION PARTS, PARTICIPATE IN A SURVEY, PURCHASE SOMETHING FROM US, REQUEST A CATALOG OR ENTER ANY OF OUR CONTESTS OR PROMOTIONS, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS. AS WE UPDATE AND EXPAND OUR SERVICES, THIS POLICY MIGHT CHANGE, SO CHECK IT OUT FROM TIME TO TIME.
The Information We Collect.
At DEMOLITION PARTS (demolitionparts.com) you can do a variety of things! You may be able to order products, enter contests, participate in surveys, vote in polls, or subscribe to a service. The types of personally identifiable information (i.e. information that can directly identify you or indicate where you might be contacted) that may be collected at these pages includes: name, address, age, date of birth, sex, grade level, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. You can view or change your information at any time by sending an email to info@demolitionparts.com.
Sometimes you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name, e-mail address, and/or address to order a gift online and want it sent directly to a friend. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient’s name, address, age, date of birth, grade level, e-mail address, sex and telephone number.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows ’98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online or Earthlink).
How We Use and Disclose Your Personal Information.
We will use the personal information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of us using your personal information for the purpose(s) submitted include if you order a catalog, we will send to you a catalog in the mail or if you have won a contest, sending to you an email notification that you have won. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to ask you to participate in a survey. For example, we may send to you an e-mail regarding special merchandise offers and announcements about products or services offered by DEMOLITION PARTS. We may also contact you offline. For example, when you provide your mailing address, DEMOLITION PARTS may send to you in the mail special offers, promotions and catalogs, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please contact us at info@demolitionparts.com
How We Share Your Personal Information.
We will not share the personal information you provide except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it; (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another); (d) with other persons or companies with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the site); and/or (e) notifying you when we make changes to one of our subscriber agreements or this policy.
Examples of us sharing your personal information for the purposes submitted are if you request information regarding financial aid, we may provide the information provided to a third party lender so that they can send to you directly the information you requested or, if you enter a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by a third party, we may forward your information to that third party. Additionally, with your consent, we may share certain of the personal information you provide online with companies not affiliated with us (i.e. third party companies) who are interested in marketing their products or services to you or in asking you questions, both online and offline. Such companies may include consumer products, telecom, financial, military, market research, entertainment, and educational services companies and their third party service providers. If you want us to stop sharing your personal information with these companies, please contact us at info@demolitionparts.com. If you consent to receiving communications from non-affiliated companies, you may need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications or if you wish to change any data you provided online. In this instance, any changes or amendments to your personal information must be given directly to each company who communicates with you as these changes, amendments and/or deletions will not be exchanged between us and non-affiliated companies.
We will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an “opt-in” or “opt-out” method, or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail).
If we do share personal information to a non-affiliated company, to the extent practical, we require that they protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. We cannot, however, guarantee how these non-affiliated companies will use your personal information.
Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information.
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. Sometimes we share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies.
Collection of Information by Others.
Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should check the other sites’ privacy notices since we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by them.
We may offer e-mail services, contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with non-affiliated companies. Based on our agreement with them, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that site visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. We have no control over the use of this information by these companies.
Cookies.
To enhance your online experience with us, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files placed on your hard disk by our web server to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services. You can opt to have your browser reject cookies. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our site in order to participate in certain promotions and other stuff. You should also know that companies that advertise on our web site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies.
Clickstream Data.
As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a web site’s server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to info@demolitionparts.com. We may use clickstream data as a form of non-personally identifiable information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of demolitionparts.com, how visitors navigate throughout the site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will only be used to improve our site. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate.
Supplementing Information.
From time to time we may supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address. Thus, information we obtain through demolitionparts.com may be intermingled with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than demolitionparts.com, including both offline and online sources.
Discussions and Community Tools.
We may, from time to time, make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups and other community tools available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for other users to view and for us to use. For example, from time to time, we may use the content you write (including your name or screen name if you post it) for promotional purposes, in e-mail newsletters or elsewhere, and by using demolitionparts.com, and/or these chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups, and other community tools, you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone – not just us – may use publicly posted information.
Our Commitment to Security.
We believe we have in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online as well as offline. When your personal information is passed onto non-affiliated companies, to the extent practical, we require that they also have in place the appropriate safeguards. We cannot, however, guarantee that they do so.
International Users.
If you are visiting demolitionparts.com from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, your orders placed through demolitionparts.com will be fully processed in and shipped from the United States and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using demolitionparts.com, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of California and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the State of California.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information.
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, please send an e-mail to info@demolitionparts.com.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Special Note for Parents.
If you have concerns about this site or its services, wish to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our services, or wish to cancel your child’s membership, please contact us at info@demolitionparts.com. Our site will not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under 13 years old in violation of applicable laws. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to our site without your permission, you may contact us at info@demolitionparts.com. We have taken commercially reasonable steps to restrict use of this site to those who are at least 13 years old. We do not knowingly sell products for purchase by children and all children’s products we sell are for purchase by adults only, or with adult permission.
Transfer of Business Assets.
The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among transferred assets if DEMOLITION PARTS, any or all of its subsidiaries or affiliates or any of their assets is acquired by a third party.
Changes to this Policy. Because our business needs may change over time, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use your personally identifiable information in a way that differs from this policy, we will revise this policy as appropriate. Your continued use of our DEMOLITIONPARTS.COM following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. This policy is effective as of October 11, 2013.
How to Contact Us.
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may e-mail info@demolitionparts.com or write to the following address:
Hi,
My order No. 27469
I wonder when my order will be sent.
What is my tracking number?
Cheers!
Log in to Reply
Josh Clemens
March 27, 2017 at 8:02 am
Hey Narae, here’s your tracking number…
thank you!!
UPS Ground # 1Z59EW590358444034
Log in to Reply
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYou must be logged in to post a comment.
This site uses Akismet to reduce spam. Learn how your comment data is processed.
DEMOLITION PRO TEAM KEVIN PERAZA | JASON WATTS | DENNIS ENARSON | KRIS FOX | MIKE ‘HUCKER’ CLARK | MATT CORDOVA | RYAN ‘BIZ’ JORDAN | TYLER FERNENGEL
SINCE 2000!
Seek and you shall find…
Search for:
What are you looking for?
